A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United (B-N) (Box 156, Folder 1135)
  Items of special note in this folder include "Relief and Rehabilitation in China" (September 1944); the opening address at the National Conference of CNRRA by Director-General Tingfu F. Tsiang (September 5, 1946); and a photograph of nurses of the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA) (December 23, 1946). All of these items are found under the mark-up United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA).
- United States (A-P) (Box 156, Folder 1135A)
  Army - Mackie, T. T., 1944; Army - Stillwell, J. W., 1943; Carter, 1946; Congress - Judd, W. H., 1948; Information Service, 1947-1948 (Bouchard, M.; Director; Harris); Interior Department - Philippine Islands, 1942 (Hester; Sayre); Library of Congress, 1949-1951; Marine Corps, 1945-1946 (Bowen; Ferguson; Peck; Tsur; Turnage); Navy, 1922-1923 (Houghton); Post Office, 1950
  Items of special note in this folder include a letter of General J. W. Stillwell, found under the mark-up United States - Army.
- United States - State Department - Memos, 1942-1948 (Box 156, Folder 1136)
- United States - State Department (A-G) (Box 156, Folder 1137)
  Atcheson, George, 1937, 1941-1943; Blake, Gilson, 1943-1946; Butrick, Richard P., 1942; Caldwell, Oliver J., 1946-1949; Clattenburg, Albert E., 1943-1945; Clubb, O. Edmund, 1947-1951, 1959; Davis, Nathaniel P., 1937; Dennis, William H., 1943-1945; Dodd, William E., 1934-1937; Drumright, Everett F., 1945-1946; Fairbank, J. K., 1943; Fairbank, Wilma (Mrs. J. K. Fairbank), 1943-1945; Frank, Henry S., 1945; Freeman, Fulton, 1949; Gilpatric, D. S., 1947; Gowen, Franklin C., 1942; Green, Joseph C., 1942; Grummon, Stuart E., 1942
  Items of special note in this folder include a Denunciation of John D. Rockefeller by Chinese Communists (June 23, 1951), found under the mark-up United States - State Department - Clubb.
- United States - State Department (H-M) (Box 156, Folder 1138)
  Haering, G. J., 1947; Hamilton, Maxwell M., 1938-1942; Hanson, Haldore, 1943-1944; Holland, Kenneth, 1946; Hornbeck, Stanley, 1941-1942; Hull, Cordell, 1942; Kelley, James H., 1942-1944; Lafoon, K. S., 1942; Long, Breckinridge, 1942; Marshall, G., 1947; McConaughly, W. A., 1942; McMurray, J. V. A., 1923-1924
- United States - State Department (P-Y) (Box 156, Folder 1138A)
  Peck, Willys R., 1945; Plitt, Edwin, 1945; Salisbury, Laurence E., 1943; Smith, Donald, 1942; Thompson, Charles A., 1942; Van den Arend, F., 1941-1942; Wells, Sumner, 1942; Wright, Butler, 1923; Young, F. R., 1944
- United States - State Department (T-W) (Box 156, Folder 1139)
  Treasury Department, 1951 (Arnold); War Department, 1942-1944 (Bresee, H. F.; Surgeon General); War Department - Library, 1942, 1947-1948 (Jones, Harold W.)
- University of the State of New York - Annual Reports, 1918-1941, 1947-1948 (Box 157, Folder 1140)
- University of the State of New York - Employees (C-S) (Box 157, Folder 1141)
  Char, Florence; Conroe, Irwin A.; Downing, Augustus, 1920-1927; Ezell, Stiles D., 1955; Field, Horace L., 1933, 1945; Horner, Harlan H., 1932-1934; Lochner, Jacob L., 1951; Probes, Charles F., 1952; Soper, Wayne W., 1938-1954, 1965-1967
- University of the State of New York - Registration (Box 157, Folder 1142)
  Medical School, 1927-1955 (Ezell; Field; Graves; Greene; Heisler; Killough; Rypins); Nursing School, 1922-1939 (Burgess; Fields; Greene; Hawkins; Hodgman; Plambeck; Wolf)
  Items of special note in this folder include Handbook No. 9; and Professional Educational Medicine - including Osteopathy and Physiotherapy (March 17, 1954). Both of these items are found under the mark-up University of the State of New York - Registration - Medical Schools.
- Un-Us (Box 157, Folder 1142A)
  Universum Book Export Co., Inc., 1946-1950 (Cheer; Hsu, Hsi-fan; Ting, T. P.); Uspensky, Katherine N., 1930
- Va-Vi (Box 157, Folder 1143)
  Van Hasselt, Jacob A. K., 1932; Vault, 1929-1934; Veghte, Adeline, 1948-1949; Vincent, George E., 1918-1933; Visitors (Langmuir, Irving, 1934; Macmillan, L., 1921; Pappenheimer, A. M., 1931)
- Visiting Professors (B-V) (Box 157, Folder 1144)
  Brackett, Elliott G., 1922; Carlson, A. J., 1934-1935; Cohn, Alfred E., 1922-1925, 1933; Frazier, Charles H., 1926; Van Slyke, Donald, 1922, 1939-1940, 1971
- Visiting Professors - Memos, 1922-1926, 1931, 1938 (Box 157, Folder 1145)
  Andrews, C.; Cochrane; Cort, W. W.; Embree; Goodrich; Greene
- Visiting Professors - Refused Appointment (B- M) (Box 157, Folder 1146)
  Barnes, M. E., 1948; Bensley, R. R., 1923; Blackfan, K., 1928; Bloomfield, Arthur L., 1927, 1940; Brenneman, J., 1939; Brumpt, E., 1935; De Schweinitz, G. E., 1927, 1938; Dochez, A. R., 1924-1925, 1948; Dock, William, 1948; DuBois, B. W., 1940; Edsall, D. L., 1927; Ewing, James, 1939; Gay, F. P., 1928, 1933; Goodpasture, E. W., 1928; Graham, E., 1939-1940; Ham, Thomas H., 1948; Hektoen, L., 1928; Heuer, G. J., 1927, 1930; Hill, A. V., 1932-1933; Karsner, H. T., 1928; Landsteiner, K., 1929; Libman, E., 1927; McMurrich, J. P., 1932; Mellanby, E., 1948; Michaelis, L., 1924-1926; Mosher, H. P., 1918-1925; Musser, J. H., 1940
- Visiting Professors - Refused Appointment (N-W) (Box 157, Folder 1147)
  Newman, A., 1932; Richards, D. W., 1948; Sabin, F. R., 1923; Scammon, R. E., 1932; Spink, W. W., 1948; Steindler, A., 1939-1940; Stenstrom, W., 1929; Swift, H. F., 1927-1928; Wells, H. G., 1928; Wilkins, R. W., 1948
- Visiting Professors - Considered Only (A-W) (Box 158, Folder 1148)
  Ashoff; Avery; Barr; Bloomfield; Brofenbrenner; Brooks; Brown; Crowe; Cushing; Director; DuBois; Ewing; Exner; Goodrich; Graff; Greene; Gregg; Holloway; Houghton; Karsner; Krasnogorsky; Leake; Longscope; Majir; Mallory; Maxey; McCoy; McIntosh; Miura; Miyajima; Newsholme; Pirquet; Powers; Resident Director; Richards; Rivers; Sabin; Saiki; Schilder; Schultz; Smith; Taliaferro; Todd; Van Slyke; Visiting Nurses; Warburg; Whipple
- Von Koenigswald, G. H. R., 1939-1940, 1945-1946 (Box 158, Folder 1148A)
- Wah - Wang, S. C. (Box 158, Folder 1149)
  Wah Chang Trading Corp., 1947 (Hu, T. C.); Walker, Mildred, 1927-1928, 1933-1938, 1955, 1963, 1971; Wang, C. C., 1922-1923; Wang, Cheng-ting, 1937; Wang, Chih-chun, 1946; Wang, Chung-ching, 1918-1919; Wang, C. T., 1923; Wang, Elsie, 1922; Wang, Hsiang-wen, 1927, 1933; Wang, Kai-wen, 1921-1923; Wang, Li-king, 1928; Wang, (Wen-pin) Paul, 1945; Wang, Rosalind S. H., 1948, 1954; Wang, S. K., 1948; Wang S. T., 1943; Wang, Shih-chieh, 1944; Wang, Shih-chun, 1933-1939, 1951-1956
  Items of special note in this folder include a translation of the transmission of the Jen Shou Medal, on the occasion of the formal opening of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), found under the mark-up Wang, Kai-wen.
- Wang, S. K. - Warren (Box 158, Folder 1150)
  Wang, Shih-kwei, 1948; Wang, Shih-wei, 1929-1930; Wang, Stephen H. H., 1933-1937, 1944-1950, 1960; Wang, Ta-e, 1945; Warren, Shields, 1948-1951
- Wartime Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 158, Folder 1151)
  Balfour; Chu; Debevoise; Forkner; Sze; Tsur; Wong
- Wartime Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 158, Folder 1152)
- Was-Wer (Box 158, Folder 1153)
  Washington University (Cowdry, E. V., 1943-1947; Graham, E. A., 1947); Watson, E. P., 1924-1926; Weekly Calendar (see Publications - "Weekly Calendar/News Bulletin"); Weiss, Siegfried, 1947, 1953; Welch, William H., 1915, 1918-1925, 1929-1930, 1934 (see also Elsmith); Weng, Hsin-chih, 1946; Wenham Memorial Fund, 1922-1924, 1946; Wershub, Leonard P., 1955
- West China Union University, 1942-1947 (Box 158, Folder 1154)
  Dentistry, School of; Leper Hospital; Medicine and Dentistry, School of; Neuropsychiatry; Obstetrics and Gynecology; Pharmacy, Department of; Physiology, Department of; Public Health and Hygiene, Department of
- West China Union University (A-H) (Box 159, Folder 1155)
  Arnold, Charles H., 1947; Arnup, Jesse H., 1945-1944; Balfour, Marshall, 1943-1946; Beech, 1938; Best, A. E., 1943; Chang, Stephen, 1944-1945; Cunningham, E. R., 1943-1945; Dsang, Lincoln, 1943; Evans, C. A., 1944-1946; Fisher, F., 1945; Forkner, C. E., 1943-1945; Hsieh, H. H., 1945
- West China Union University (Ki-Th) (Box 159, Folder 1156)
  Kilborn, Leslie G., 1943-1947; Liljestrand, S. Harry, 1944-1945; Lindsay, Ashley W., 1943-1949; Littley, Albert F., 1943; Priest, Elsie M., 1944-1946; Robertson, H. D., 1945; Small, William W., 1944-1945; Thompson, J. Claude, 1942
- West China Union University (Ti-Yu) (Box 159, Folder 1157)
  Ting, Te-peng, 1944-1946; Tsao, (Chung-liang) Clifford, 1944; Welch, Herbert, 1943; Wilford, E. C., 1943-1949; Yu, Huan-wen, 1943-1944
- White - Wong, K. K. L. (Box 159, Folder 1158)
  White, Jennifer (Mrs. James D. White), 1942; White, J. G., Engineering Corp. (see Survey Engineering); Wilmington General Hospital - Hockett, A. J., 1947; Wilson, George G., 1916-1917, 1920-1925, 1932-1937, 1941-1942, 1947-1950; Wilson, Stanley D., 1962, 1971; Women's Hospital, 1916-1917; Wong, Davina (Mrs.), 1954; Wong, H. S., 1924; Wong, K. C., 1947; Wong, Kamehameha Kun-lai, 1947-1954
- Wong, Wen-hao, 1929-1942 (Box 159, Folder 1159)
- Wong, Wen-hao, 1943-1950 (Box 159, Folder 1160)
- Wong, Y. T. - Wu, P. C. (Box 159, Folder 1161)
  Wong, Yan-tim (Timothy), 1946-1948, 1952; Woo, K. F., 1946-1947, 1953; Woo, L. S., 1945-1946; Wood, Ruth A., 1947; Woodward, Robert S., 192;1 World Health Organization (Chu, C. K., 1948-1953, 1958; Fang, I. C., 1950; Lambert, Robert A., 1949-1951); Wright, Irving S., 1944; Wu, Alfred Chieh-ping, 1947; Wu, Chen-fu, 1945; Wu, Laurence Tien-fu, 1949-1952; Wu, Lien-the, 1921, 1930, 1934-1935; Wu, Pao-chen, 1947
- Wu, S. C. - Wu, Y. S. (Box 160, Folder 1162)
  Wu, Shao-ching, 1943-1949, 1963; Wu, Te-leng, 1948-1949; Wu, Wai-ping, 1947; Wu, Yi-fang, 1944; Wu, Yi-cheng, 1946
- Yai-Yen (Box 160, Folder 1163)
  Yai, Guna-tilaka, 1966; Yale in China, 1943, 1947; Yang, Ching-po, 1930-1931, 1952-1953; Yang, Chun-li, 1949-1950; Yang, Kui-lan, 1925; Yang, Stephen, 1946-1948; Yang, Wang, 1944; Yau, Yuvan, 1926-1928; Yee, James, 1939-1941, 1945-1951, 1954; Yen, F. C., 1927; Yen, L. C., 1943 ;Yen, W. W., 1923-1925, 1930-1932, 1946-1947
- Yenching University (Box 160, Folder 1164)
  General, 1932, 1942, 1945; Bachman, George, 1943; Ballou, 1945; Chang, H. C., 1930, 1961; Forkner, C. E., 1943-1944; Gee, Nathaniel G., 1938; Greene, 1927-1929, 1934; Hsu, Leonard S., 1937; Luh, C. W., 1950; Mei, Yi-pao, 1943, 1959; Stuart, Leighton, 1946-1947, 1952; Tsai, Stephen, 1946-1947, 1952; Tsai, Stephen, 1946, 1958; Wilson, Stanley D., 1926-1927, 1943-1955; Yu, Shao-chen, 1946-1948, 1954-1958; Yu, Shao-chi, 1945-1953; Yu, Sung-ting, 1944
  Items of special note in this folder include a memorial to N. G. Gee.
- Yo-Yu (Box 160, Folder 1165)
  Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1946 (Hoover, Lyman); Yu, Cho-ale, 1950; Yu, Horace, 1947-1949; Yu, Pen-chung, 1946-1948; Yu, Tao-chen, 1955; Yu, Tsai-fan, 1948-1949, 1952-1956, 1971
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Pen-chung Yu.
- Yu Wang Fu Association, 1928-1941 (Box 160, Folder 1166)
  Address List, 1928-1941; Chop (die)
- Yuan (Box 160, Folder 1167)
  Yuan, Catherine, 1946-1947; Yuan, T. L., 1931, 1951
  Items of special note in this folder include an invitation to the opening of the National Library (1931), found under the mark-up Yuan, T. L.
- Z (Box 160, Folder 1168)
  Zinsser, R. Hans, 1927, 1932-1933, 1938-1940; Zucker, A. E., 1968; Zurovec, Josef, 1932
- China Medical Board, Inc. (CMB) - Financial Data, 1943-1945 (Box 160, Folder 1168A)
- Contract Settlement Checks, Nos. 1-1986, August 15, 1946 (Box 161, Folder 1169)
  See also Box 35, Folder 246
- Anatomy - Staff - Stevenson, P. H. - Envelope (Box 162, Folder 1)
  Attached to letter from Lockhart, June 12, 1937.
  See also Box 12, Folder 78
- Architectural Service Bureau - Plot Plans (Box 162, Folder 2)
  Small scale plot plans
  See also Box 12, Folder 83
- Budget - 1938/39 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  See also Box 16, Folder 114
- Budget - 1939/40 (Box 162, Folder 4)
- Budget - 1940/41 (Box 162, Folder 5)
- Budget - 1941/42 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  See also Box 17, Folder 115
- Budget - Correspondence - Dunlap (Box 162, Folder 7)
  Chart, attached to letter from Dunlap to Kirk, January 6, 1920.
  See also Box 17, Folder 117
- Budget - Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Summary of Proposed Budget Changes - By Departments, 1935/36-1936/37. Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Analysis of Payroll Increases Proposed by Department Heads, 1936-1937.
  See also Box 18, Folder 124
- Cenozic Laboratory - Chart (Box 162, Folder 9)
  Statement of Compensation Payable to Employees in Liquidation of Contracts as of January 31, 1942.
  See also Box 19, Folder 130
- Diploma - 1929 - Nursing (Box 162, Folder 10)
  See also Box 41, Folder 291
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Chinese Character Stamp (Box 162, Folder 11)
  See also Box 48, Folder 335
- Ferguson - Silk Letter (Box 162, Folder 12)
  See also Box 57, Folder 397
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Chart (Box 162, Folder 13)
  Attached to letter from Greene to Eggleston, November 9, 1934. Total Expenditures Peking Union Medical Center (PUMC) 3212 - Human Paleontological Research in Asia - April 1, 1933-March 31, 1934. Consolidated Statement
  See also Box 57, Folder 403
- Greene - Diary (Box 162, Folder 14)
  Hsieh-Ho. A free publication by Peking Union Medical Center (PUMC) Student Association, June 16, 1925.
  See also Box 62, Folder 439
- Handbook - Maps (Box 162, Folder 15)
  2 copies of Cook's Tourist Skeleton Map of Peking and 1 copy of Map of Peking.
  See also Box 65, Folder 461
- Health Station - Envelope (Box 162, Folder 16)
  See also Box 66, Folder 465
- Nurses - Chart (Box 162, Folder 17)
  Places from which Nursing Staff of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) retiring 1928-1933 were recruited. A considerable portion of these returned to the institutions from which they came.
  See also Box 98, Folder 706
- Physics - Staff - Stifler - Ads (Box 162, Folder 18)
  Attached to letter, October 5, 1918.
  See also Box 121, Folder 881
- Pre-Medical School - Chart, March 1921 (Box 162, Folder 19)
  See also Box 126, Folder 913
- Property - Insurance - Chart (Box 162, Folder 20)
  See also Box 127, Folder 919
- Publications - "Unison" (bulletin), 1941 (Box 162, Folder 21)
  See also Box 129, Folder 945
- Publicity - Broadside (Box 162, Folder 22)
  See also Box 132, Folder 958
- Rockefeller Foundation - Information Service Article by Vincent, News Release, 3 copies (Box 162, Folder 23)
  "An American Medical College in Peking"
  See also Box 139, Folder 999
- Salaries - Memo - Chart (Box 162, Folder 24)
  Attached to memo by Stifler, March 25, 1921. Chart: Salaries by department, position, year - 1921-1926.
  See also Box 141, Folder 1017
- Statistics - Alumni - Charts (Box 162, Folder 25)
  Chart I: Distribution of Graduates of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), as of July 1, 1933 (includes Medical Graduates and Nursing Graduates). Chart II: Places from which Graduate and Departmental Students were Sent to Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) for study, 1921-1933. Chart III: Places from which Nursing Staff of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) retiring 1928-1933 were recruited. A considerable portion of these returned to the institutions from which they came.
  See also Box 144, Folder 1046
- Unidentified Chinese Character Stamp, undated (Box 162, Folder 26)
- Houghton, Henry S. (Box 163, Folder 1)
  Diary - Index, 1920-1921; Journal - Index, 1921-1924
  See also Box 73, Folders 511 and 514-516.
- Lantern Slides - Index (Box 163, Folder 2)
- Dedication - Newspaper Clipping, 1921 (Box 165, Folder A)
- Neurology - Staff - Lyman - "Neuropsychiatry in Peiping", 1932-1935 (Box 165, Folder B)
  See also Box 97, Folder 696.
- Photographs, 1917-1968 (Box 165, Folder C)
- Photographs - List of Where Used (Box 165, Folder D)
- Photographs - Lantern Slide List (Box 165, Folder E)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record, 1937-1950 (Box 166)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record Index, 1916-1950 (Box 166)
- Minutes of the Peking Union Medical College, 1928-1929 (Box 166)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes 1-VI, numbers 1-45, 1916-1921 (Box 167)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes VII-IX, numbers 46-73, 1922-1924 (Box 167)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes X-XII, numbers 74-100, 1925-1927 (Box 168)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes XIII-XIV, numbers 101-139, 1928-1929 (Box 168)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes XV-XVI, numbers 140-184a, 1930-1931 (Box 168)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volumes XVII, numbers 185-205, 1932 (Box 169)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record - Volume XVIII, numbers 206-217, 1933 (Box 169)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record, 1934 (Box 169)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record, 1935 (Box 170)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Documents of Record, 1936 (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1936 January (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1936 April (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1936 July (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1936 October (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1937 January (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1937 April (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1937 July (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1937 October (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1938 July (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1939 January (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1939 April (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1939 July (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1939 October (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1940 January (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1940 April (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1940 July (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1940 October (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1941 January (Box 170)
- Nursing Journal of China, 1941 April (Box 170)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications, 1924-1925 (Box 171)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (G-Z), 1926-1927 (Box 172)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (H-Z), 1927-1928 (Box 173)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-H), 1928-1929 (Box 174)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (I-X), 1928-1929 (Box 175)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-F), 1929-1930 (Box 176)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-H), 1930-1931 (Box 176)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (I-N), 1930-1931 (Box 177)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (O-S), 1930-1931 (Box 177)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (F-K), 1931-1932 (Box 178)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (L-X), 1931-1932 (Box 178)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-H), 1932-1933 (Box 179)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (E-G), 1933-1934 (Box 179)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (H-X), 1933-1934 (Box 180)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-E), 1934-1935 (Box 180)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (J-X), 1934-1935 (Box 180)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (J-X), 1935-1936 (Box 181)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-H), 1936-1937 (Box 181)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Publications - (A-G), 1938-1939 (Box 182)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Bibliography of Publications, 1915-1940 (Box 182)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1918-1921 (Box 183)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1921-1922 (Box 183)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1922-1923 (Box 183)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1923-1924 (Box 184)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1925-1926 (Box 184)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-F), 1926-1927 (Box 184)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-G), 1927-1928 (Box 185)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (G-L), 1929-1930 (Box 186)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (M-X), 1929-1930 (Box 187)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-E), 1931-1932 (Box 188)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (I-X), 1932-1933 (Box 189)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-D), 1933-1934 (Box 189)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (F-I), 1934-1935 (Box 190)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-E), 1935-1936 (Box 190)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (F-I), 1935-1936 (Box 190)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (I-X), 1936-1937 (Box 191)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-B), 1937-1938 (Box 191)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (C-E), 1937-1938 (Box 192)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (F-H), 1937-1938 (Box 192)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (I-X), 1937-1938 (Box 192)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (H-S), 1938-1939 (Box 193)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (A-D), 1939-1940 (Box 193)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (E-H), 1939-1940 (Box 194)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications - (I-X), 1939-1940 (Box 194)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Publications, 1940 (Box 195)
- China Medical Board 100th Anniversary publication, 2014 (Box 196)
- Duplicates - Dedication Volume, 1921 (Box D 1, Folder 1)
  Duplicate Material.
- Duplicates - Plot Plan of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (Box D 1, Folder 2)
- Duplicates - Outline of the Organization of the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (Private), 3 copies (Box D 1, Folder 3)
- Duplicates - Davidson Black, 1884-1934 - Memorial, 2 copies (Box D 1, Folder 4)
- Duplicates - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Historical Sketch and Description of Buildings, 1922 (Box D 1, Folder 5)
- Duplicates - Yearbook - "The Unison", 1927 (Box D 1, Folder 6)
- Duplicates - "Medicine in China" - Rockefeller Foundation, China Medical Commission, 1914 (Box D 1, Folder 7)
- Duplicates - Bulletin of Information for Prospective Student, 1932 (Box D 1, Folder 8)
- Duplicates - Hsien Wu, 1893-1959 - Memorial (Box D 1, Folder 9)
- Duplicates - "Your Opportunity" - Publication of the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) School of Nursing (Box D 1, Folder 10)
- Duplicates - Programme of the Medical Conference, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), September 15-22, 1921; 3 copies (Box D 1, Folder 11)
- Duplicates - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Announcements - Medical School/Nursing School/Hospital (Box D 2, Folder 12)
- Duplicates - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Announcements - Medical School/Nursing School/Hospital (Box D 3, Folder 13)
- Duplicates - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Announcements - Medical School/Nursing School/Hospital (Box D 4, Folder 14)
- Duplicates - China Medical Board, Inc. - Annual Reports (Box D 4, Folder 15)
- Duplicates - Bibliography of the Publications from the Laboratories and Clinics of the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (Box D 4, Folder 16)
- "Spirit Ramp" at Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Large format material, housed in map folder. (Folder No Folder)
- General Drawings - Complete Set, 1917; Large format material, housed in map folder. (Drawer C 11, Folder 68, Item 1)
  Blueprints.